Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory10 Mss.B.B61.inventory10
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents O
  - Oustinoff, Mikhael M. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept.24
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 17
  - Outes, F.F. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1931 July; 1p.
  - Outhwaite, Leonard (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 17; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - Leonard Outhwaite -- from F. Krause, 1932 Nov. 14
  - Outlook, The (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 2; 1p.
  - Overbergh, Cyr. van (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1905 May 15; 2p.
  - Overholser, Winfred (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 3; 1p.
  - Overstreet, H.A. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Ovington, Mary White (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1910 June 21
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p.
  - Owen, Richard (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 23
  - Owen, Robert L. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 4; 1p.
      (Enc: Owen, R.L. to Aall, H.H.)
    - Owen, Robert L. -- to H.H. Aall, 1925 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Owen, R.L., Dec. 4, 1925)
  - Owre, J. Riis (Box 68)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies. Jan. 1938., 1938 Feb. 8; 1p.
  - Oxford University Press (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
      See Nicholson, Margaret
  - Oyengan, H.R. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 8; 1p.
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents P
  - PM Editor (Box 68)
    - See Boas, F. to N.Y. Post, Nov.27, 1941, 1941 Dec. 2; 1p.
  - Pacific Science Congress (Box 68)
    - See Cook. S.J., Apr.10, 1931
    - See Jenness, D., May 8, 1930
    - See Cook, S.J. to Barrows, A.L., 1931 Oct. 28
  - Pack, Oscar T. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
  - Packard, A.S. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 24; 1p.
  - Packard, Phoebe E. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 2p.
  - Padelford, Frederick M. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept.27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 10; 1p.
    - Frederick M. Padelford -- to L.P. Sieg, 1940 June 10; 1p.
    - (Enc: with Sieg, L.P., June 11, 1940)
  - Page, Curtis Hidden (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1905 May 15
  - Pagenstecher, A. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1904 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 10; 1p.
  - Pagenstecher, Rudolf (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 July 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p.
  - Paget, R.A.S. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1928 May 13; 4p.
  - Palacios, G.D. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1915
  - Palencias?, A. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1914 Sept.28; 1p.
  - Palestine Academy of Sciences (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 8; 4p.
  - Palliardi, Marie (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 9; 1p.
  - Palmer, Archie M. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 22; 1p.
    - Archie M. Palmer -- from H.E. Erdman, 1927 Nov. 1; 1p.
  - Palmer, Carroll E. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1941 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 17; 1p.
  - Paltsits, Victor H. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 9
  - Palumbo, Vicente (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 24; 1p.
  - Pan American Union (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 24; 1p.
  - Pana, Porfirio (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1911 June 12
    - From Boas, 1911 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1911 Nov. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1911 May 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 May 6
    - To Boas, 1911 June 25
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 May 21
  - Pancoast, George W. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1900 July 7
    - To Boas, 1900 Aug. 31
  - Panconcalli-Calzia -- - see Calzia, G. (Box 68)
  - Panhuye, Edwan (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 14
  - Pani, Alberto J. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1911 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1912 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1912 Apr. 18
    - From Boas, 1912 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 6; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. end; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 June 30
  - Panofsky, Erwin (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 21; 1p.
  - Panse? (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 22; 1p
    - (Enc: with Kallmann, Franz, Oct. 26, 1936)
  - Panth, Bhola D. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1942 Aug. 26; 1p.
  - Pape, A. G. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 30; 2p.
  - Pappe, N. (Box 68)
    - See Winnikow, T., Apr. 15, 1930
  - Pappenheimer, Alwin M. (Box 68)
    - Feb. 25, 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 2; 2p.
  - Parachdreit? (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 19; 2p.
  - Paris. National Library (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 10; 1p.
  - Paris. University (Box 68)
    See Lapie, Paul
  - Park, Prof. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1939 Sept. 22; 1p.
  - Park, Marion (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. end
    - (see Baker, Frank E. Open letter), 1940 Dec. 5; 1p.
  - Park, Robert E. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - Robert E. Park -- to I. Singer, 1907 May 28
  - Park, Willard Z. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept.24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 10; 1p.
  - Parker, James (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 9
  - Parker, A. K. (Box 68)
    - A.K. Parker -- to Keppel, 1906 Sept. 6
  - Parker, Beryl (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 31; 1p.
    - see Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Parker, Frances W. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1888 Sept. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Sept.16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 11; 2p.
  - Parker, G. E. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p.
  - Parker, James & Co. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 22; 1p.
  - Parker, Valeria H. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 3; 2p.
  - Parker, V.L.N. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1937 July 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1937 July 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Uhl, Byron H. to Pidelity and Deposit Co. of Md.7-9-37), 1937 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1937 July 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 27; 1p.
  - Parker & Son (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 1; 1p.
  - Parmelee, Maurice (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 19; 2p.
  - Parrish, Mrs. Maxfield (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 29; 1p.
  - Parrlini, P.E. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 21; 1p.
  - Parrott, Frances (Box 68)
    - Frances Parrott -- to A.M. Tozzer, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p.
  - Parsons, Charles L. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 16; 2p.
  - Parsons, A.T.L. (Mrs. Edgerton) (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p.
  - Parsons, Elsie Clews (Mrs. Herbert) (Box 69)
    Native American Images note
    Folder #16: Pueblo prayer stick
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 14; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept.28
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1917 May 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9
    - From Boas, 1917 May 25
    - From Boas, 1917 May 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 June 5
    - From Boas, 1917 June 12
    - From Boas, 1917 July 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 23; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 26; 6p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 June 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept.4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept.17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept.30
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1925 June 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 July 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 5; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1925 July 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 June 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Sept.23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Sept.30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept.27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 July 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept.3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept.23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept.29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept.30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Sept.11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 18; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Sept.17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 July 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 July 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 May 26
    - To Boas, 1917 May 30
    - To Boas, 1917 June 11
    - To Boas, 1917 June 23
    - To Boas, 1917 July 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept.11
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept.1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1919 May 9
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1920 June 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 7; 2p.
    - (Enc: Huntington, A.M. to Parsons, Elsie Cews, June 1, 1920), 1920 Aug. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept.4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 19; 2p.
    - on FB's letter Oct.5 - to her, 1920 Oct.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 24; 2p.
      (Enc: List of names)
    - on FB's letter Nov.4 to her, 1920 Nov.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept.8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept.24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept.; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 June 18; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1925 July 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 5; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept.28; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - on FB's letter May 16 to her, 1927 May
    - To Boas, 1927 June 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept.30; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 11; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 4; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept.1; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept.28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug.; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept.13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept.29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 21; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept.18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - on FB's letter Feb. 15 to her, 1934 Feb.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 23; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept.2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept.8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 July 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept.1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept.2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. end; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. end; 2p.
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from M.W. Beckwith, 1921 Dec. 12; 2p.
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- to W.M. Calder, 1917 Nov. 3
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from W.M. Calder, 1917 Dec. 19
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- to W.H. Carpenter, 1917 Mar. 27
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from Paul Fuller, 1920 Sept.27; 1p.
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from F.H. Gillett, 1929 June 14
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from F.H. Gillett, 1929 June 21
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from P.E. Goddard, 1925 June 29
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from P.M. Hayden, 1933 Nov. 2
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from M.J. Herskovits, 1937 Aug. 30
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- to A.M. Huntington, 1917 June 11
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from A.M. Huntington, 1920 June 1; 2p.
    - (Enc: Parsons, E.C. to Boas, F., Aug. 7, 1920)
    - E.C. Parsons -- to Gov. Frank (Harrison), Mar. 19, 1919
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- to A.M. Huntington, 1925
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from T.J.Jones, 1924 Dec. 19
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- to Schiff, 1921 Aug. 12; 2p.
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- to Schiff, 1921 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- to M.W.Stirling, 1932 Sept.13; 2p.
    - Elsie Cews Parsons -- from A.M. Tozzer, 1923 Dec. 19; 1p.
  - Parsons, E.T. (Box 69)
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept.27
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 20
  - Parsons, Frederick W. (Box 69)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - (Enc: Kallmann, F. Memorandum about manner and purpose of intended research work, Dec. 6, 1936)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - Frederick W. Parsons -- to Maurice J. Karpf, 1935 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - (Enc. with letter from Malzberg, Benjamin to Boas, F., dated 1-31-35 dated 1-31-35)
  - Parsons, Harry H. (Box 69)
    - 1913 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1932 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept.28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 27; 1p.
  - Parsons, Herbert (Box 69)
    - Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - (Enc. Parsons, H. to Bondy,W., Bondy, W. to Parsons, H., Nov. 11, 1920 - Nov. 16, 1920)
    - Herbert Parsons -- to W. Bondy, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally with Parsons, H. to Boas, F., Nov.17, 1920)
    - Herbert Parsons -- from Bondy, W., 1920 Nov. 16; 1p.